boxrox.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy | BOXROX

The privacy and security of your personal information is extremely important to us. This privacy policy in combination with our Cookies Policy explains how and why we use your personal data, so you can be confident about giving us your information. This policy applies if you are a visitor (reader, writer, volunteer, customer, employee) of our website, use any of our services, email, call or write to us. If you do not agree or not wish to be bound by our privacy policy, you are not authorized to access or otherwise use the websites, or take part in any of the offers and services that we provide. In certain circumstances we may also provide an extra privacy notice, which will always refer to this page.

We will update the table of content as soon as possible.

In this policy, whenever you see the words ‘we’, ‘us’, ‘our’, ‘BOXROX’ or ‘eCom 360’, it refers to:

 **eCom 360 UG (haftungsbeschränkt)**  
c/o BOXROX  
Alte Schönhauser Str. 38  
10119 Berlin, Germany

Telephone: +49 30 6800 9500  
E-Mail: info@boxrox.com

eCom 360 is the operating company behind the BOXROX brand (EU Trade mark number 012816922) and it’s services. The BOXROX brand primarily acts as a digital news and content publisher which offers quality journalism for special interest groups. Beside editorial content BOXROX offers different information services around special interest groups.

We are committed to managing & safeguarding your personal information in accordance with current legislation and best practice. Our aim is to be responsible, relevant and secure when using your data. Whenever you provide personal information we will treat that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We will process the personal information you have supplied to us to conduct and manage our business to enable us to give you the most appropriate marketing, information, service and products and provide the best and most secure experience. These are what we consider to be our ‘Legitimate Interests’. We endeavor at all times to keep your data accurate and secure, and to honor your data preferences with regard to receipt of direct marketing e.g. postal communications, email, mobile messaging and telephone calls.

We operate websites that may contain hyperlinks to websites owned and operated by third parties. These third party websites have their own privacy policies, and are also likely to use cookies, and we therefore urge you to review them. They will govern the use of personal information you submit when visiting these websites, which may also be collected by cookies. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of such third party websites and your use of such websites is at your own risk.

We may use third party suppliers to provide part of our service to you. In some circumstances these providers may be based in countries outside the European Economic Area whose laws provide for a different standard of protection for your personal information than that provided under German Law. In such circumstances: 

  * We will only transfer your personal data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission. For further details, see [European Commission: Adequacy of the protection of personal data in non-EU countries](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/adequacy-protection-personal-data-non-eu-countries_en).
  * Where we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe. For further details, see [European Commission: Model contracts for the transfer of personal data to third countries](https://ec.europa.eu/info/strategy/justice-and-fundamental-rights/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/model-contracts-transfer-personal-data-third-countries_en).
  * Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between the Europe and the US. For further details, see [European Commission: EU-US Privacy Shield](https://ec.europa.eu/info/strategy/justice-and-fundamental-rights/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/eu-us-privacy-shield_en).

If you would like further information about the specific mechanism, used by us when transferring your personal data out of the EEA please contact: [privacy@boxrox.com](mailto:privacy@boxrox.com)

Your personal data will not be disclosed to state institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. Before we release data on this basis, we will ensure that the information is being provided to a genuine and properly authorized investigation.

We reserve the right to revise or amend this Privacy Policy at any time to reflect changes to our business or changes in the law. Where these changes are significant we will endeavor to email all of our registered users to make sure that they are informed of such changes. However, it is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy before each use of the Website.

If you are accessing our website to consume content (e.g. news, article, posts, etc.) or use other information services, the personal data we collect may include IP, geo location, browser and device details, physical and email addresses via an online registration/request form, as well as usage information about your use of the website and services as well as your use of any newsletters or other communication you agree to receive following your visit to the website.

Anonymous data will be recorded for the purpose of reporting web traffic statistics, advertisement ‘click-throughs’, and/or other activities on our sites. We may receive information about you from any third parties we may partner with through the use of cookie technologies to personalize advertisements for goods and services (please see Marketing and Advertising below for further information). To opt out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests by our partners, visit the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance at <http://youronlinechoices.eu/>

Sometimes we will ask you for additional personal information, and sometimes sensitive personal information (e.g. if you’ve entered a competition or sent in your story to be used in our magazine or for publicity). When we do this we only use the personal information with your explicit consent, and we will provide further information at the time about why we’re collecting your information and how we’ll use it.

If you are an EU data subject, our site provides you the opportunity to consent to our use of your personal information prior to submitting any personal information; We will only use your personal information if you consent to such use.

For detailed information on Cookies we use please see our Cookie Policy.

We may use the information you share with us and the information we collect through your use of our sites in different areas described below and as described at the time of capture.

## Infrastructure and Hosting

### Web Hosting

Our IT infrastructure (web server, database, domain name) is provided by, ALL-INKL refers to ALL-INKL.COM – Neue Medien Münnich, Hauptstraße 68, 02742 Friedersdorf, Germany and Hetzner refers to Hetzner Online GmbH, Industriestr. 25, 91710 Gunzenhausen, Germany. Both providers are based and host there servers in Germany. Both provider act under the of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (GDPR) therefore Data Processing Agreement have been closed with ALL-INKL and Hetzner.

#### Log files

We, or our hosting provider, collects on the basis of our legitimate interests on every access to the server on which this service is located (so-called server log files). The access data includes name of the may retrieved web page, file, date and time of retrieval, amount of data transferred, message about successful retrieval, browser type and version, the user’s operating system, referrer URL (the previously visited page), IP address and the requesting provider.

#### SSL-Encryption

We use a SSL or TLS encryption for security reasons and to protect the transmission of confidential content, such as requests and orders that you send to us as a website visitor.

#### Data Sharing

A merge of this log file data with other data sources will not be done by us or shared with any third party.

#### Data Retention Time

Log file information is stored for security purposes (for example, to investigate abusive or fraudulent activities). We keep log file data as long as necessary and never longer than the terms of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (GDPR) including any implementing data protection legislation in Germany allows. Data whose further retention is required for evidential purposes shall be exempted from the cancellation until final clarification of the incident.

## Statistics and Performance

### Google Analytics

Our websites uses Google Analytics as its primary solution for tracking website visits, interactions and events. Provider is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. We uses website analytics data to help improve the way we delivery content and online experiences to visitors.

Google is certified under the Privacy Shield Agreement, which provides a guarantee to comply with European privacy legislation ([https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)).

For full details on how Google processes your data please visit: [https://support.google.com/analytics/topic/2919631?hl=en&ref_topic=1008008](https://support.google.com/analytics/topic/2919631?hl=en&ref_topic=1008008)

#### IP-Anonymization

We have activated the function IP anonymization on our websites. As a result, your IP address will be truncated by Google within member states of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area prior to transmission to the United States. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be sent to a Google server in the US and shortened there.

On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide other services related to website activity and internet usage to the website operator. The IP address provided by Google Analytics as part of Google Analytics will not be merged with other Google data.

#### Browser-Plugin

You can prevent the storage of cookies by a corresponding setting of your browser software; however, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use all the features of this website to the fullest extent possible.

In addition, you may prevent the collection by Google of the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website (including your IP address) as well as the processing of this data by Google by downloading the browser plug-in available under the following link and install: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>.

#### Opposition to Data Collection

You can prevent the collection of your data by Google Analytics by clicking on the following link. An opt-out cookie will be set to prevent your data from being collected on future visits to this site: Disable Google Analytics

For more information on how to handle user data on Google Analytics, please refer to the Google Privacy Policy: <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en>.

#### Data Processing Agreement

We closed a Data Processing Agreement with Google. In this agreement Google commits to process user data only within the scope of the functionality of Analytics, to delete it on our instructions and to take technical and organizational measures for data security.

#### Data Retention Time

The retention of user and event data in Google Analytics is 14 months.

## Social Media

### Social Sharing Links

The content on our pages can be shared privacy-friendly in social networks such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest or Google+. Our social links not establish direct contact between the networks and users until the user actively clicks on one of these buttons or uses the Facebook commenting option for articles. Our users can share the content of this website in a privacy-compliant way on social networks without creating complete surf profiles by the network operators.

An automatic transfer of user data to the operators of these platforms is not done by us. If the user is logged in to one of the social networks, when using the social buttons of Facebook, Google+, Pinterest Twitter & Co., an information window appears in which the user can confirm the text and shared information before submitting.

### Facebook Comments

We use “Facebook Comments”, a service of Facebook Inc., 1601 S California Ave, Palo Alto, California 94304, USA (hereinafter referred to as: “Facebook”) on our website. Facebook Comments gives our users the possibility to discuss and comment our articles and content by using the social network and it’s social features. Users need to have registered Facebook account to use the comment option on our website. All comments and comment related information will be stored by Facebook inside the social network.

Our users have no direct contact with Facebook Comments only if they actively clicking on the Facebook Comment link inside the content area.

Facebook has subjected to the Privacy Shield Agreement concluded between the European Union and the United States and certified. As a result, Facebook commits to comply with the standards and regulations of European data protection law. For more information, please refer to the following linked entry: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active)

Further information from the third party on data protection can be found on the following Facebook page: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy>. Information about Facebook pixels can be found on the following Facebook page: <https://www.facebook.com/business/help/651294705016616>

## Embedded Content

We may enrich our content with different kinds of (social) media elements also called “embeds” to give our readers better journalism and quality content. Such media elements could be embedded via a HTML Iframe or a similar approaches to show media elements from a social networks (e.g. Facebook, Instagram, etc.) or video platforms (e.g. YouTube). As this kind of content is mostly hosted by third party providers personal and cookie information can be transferred to access the embedded content.

When we embed third party media we always want to full fill the requirements of the terms of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (GDPR) as well as the terms and conditions of the third party which provides and hosts the content. If third parties offer functionality or technology to embed their content in a way which supports the GDPR or the privacy of our users we keen to implement this functionality as soon as possible. For example all embedded YouTube files are using the “No Cookie” option provided by YouTube.

Our users can block different types of third party embeds by using our opt-out functionality. Further information can be found in the Cookie Policy.

## Location-based Services

Some of our information services hosted and developed by us may use details about your location and your browser/device type (e.g. desktop, tablet or mobile device) to provide you tailored content based on your located area (e.g. next gyms in your area, language area, screen resolution). We only using this information during the content selection and rendering process of our website to offer you the right content and a quality service. This information will maybe recorded anonymously for the purpose of statistics and quality control of our information service. Personal location-based information from our services will never be shared with a third party.

### Google Maps

We include maps from the Google Maps service provided by Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. The processed data may include, in particular, users’ IP addresses and location data, but these are not collected without their consent (usually as part of the settings of their mobile devices). The data can be processed in the USA. Privacy Policy: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/, opt-out: https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated.

## Marketing and Advertisement

Our website shows marketing and advertising campaigns to users. A certain amount of this advertising is tailored to the individual user, as practice known as “Online Behavioral Advertising” which uses cookies to discover general information about the pages you visit. This keeps many of our websites and services you use free of charge. Our advertising delivery systems and partners uses the limited information available to it to serve adverts to you, which it believes are relevant. It does not collect personal information such as your name, email address postal address or telephone number.

From time to time, we may share this aggregated data with our advertising partners. This could mean that when you are on other websites you are served advertising based on your behavior across our websites or you may be served advertising based on your behavior on other sites.

Behavioral retargeting is another form of Online Behavioral Advertising that enables us and some of our advertising partners to show you adverts based on browsing patterns and interactions with the site away from our sites. For example, if you have visited the website of a sports brand you may start seeing adverts from that same brand site displaying special offers or showing you the products that you were browsing. This allows companies to advertise to website visitors who leave their website without making a purchase.

If you want to opt out of receiving Online Behavioral Advertising this does not mean that you will no longer receive advertising when you are using our sites. It just means that the advertising you see will not be customized for you. If you would like more information about online behavioral targeting and how to opt out of it, please visit www.youronlinechoices.com or you can also visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>

Our websites uses JavaScript to detect the use of ad blocking extensions for web browsers, we do not store any information on users’ devices and do not  process any personal data.

### Newsletter

We will use the details you have shared to send you the newsletter to which you have subscribed. We will not add them to any marketing lists, unless you have consented to this. We will provide a way for you to unsubscribe on every newsletter we send to you. Details you share with us for the purpose of newsletter subscription will never be shared with a third party.

#### Double opt-in and logging

The registration for our newsletter takes place in a so-called double opt-in procedure. In other words, you will receive an mail after subscribing the newsletter, requesting confirmation of your registration. This confirmation is necessary so that nobody can register with external mail addresses.

The registration for the newsletter will be logged in order to prove the registration process according to the legal requirements. This includes the storage of the login and the confirmation time, as well as the IP address.

#### Hosting

We don’t use a third party provide to manage and send our newsletter to you. The newsletter is hosted and send from our hosted servers in Germany. If we going to use an external newsletter service provider, we will inform you and ask for your permission.

#### Statistics

Our newsletters contain a so-called “web-beacon”, a pixel-sized file that is retrieved from our server when the newsletter is opened. This call will initially collect technical information, such as information about the browser and your system, as well as your IP address and time of retrieval. This information is used to improve the technical performance of services based on their specifications or audience and their reading habits, based on their locations (which can be determined using the IP address) or access times.

Statistical surveys also include determining if the newsletters will be opened, when they will be opened and which links will be clicked. For technical reasons, this information can be assigned to the individual newsletter recipients. However, it is not our desire to observe individual users. The evaluations serve us much more to recognize the reading habits of our users and to adapt our content to them or to send different content according to the interests of our users.

### Direct Marketing

We may use the details you share with us to send you offers and promotions by email, post, telephone or SMS wherever we have legitimate interest grounds to do so and where you have not objected. We will provide a way for you to opt-out of receiving marketing promotions both at the time of data capture and every time we contact you thereafter. You can also email privacy@boxrox.com to request your details are suppressed from all promotional campaigns. We won’t use your personal data for marketing purposes at all if you’ve told us not to.

### Doubleclick

Our websites uses “DoubleClick” as its primary solution for online marketing and advertising. Provider is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. We use DoubleClick for marketing and optimization purposes, especially to show you relevant and interesting ads, improve campaign performance reports, or prevent you from seeing the same ads multiple times. This is also our legitimate interest in the processing of the above data, this is based on Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. The storage period is 2 years.

Google is certified under the Privacy Shield Agreement, which provides a guarantee to comply with European privacy legislation ([https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)).

For full details on how Doubleclick processes your data please visit:  
<https://www.google.com/doubleclick> and

Google uses cookie IDs to determine which ads are shown in which web browser. This can prevent ads from appearing multiple times. DoubleClick can also use the cookie IDs to track conversions related to ad requests. For example, if you see a DoubleClick ad and later use the same web browser to visit the advertiser’s website and buy something there. According to Google, the aforementioned cookies contain no personal data. By using DoubleClick, your browser automatically establishes a direct connection to the Google server. We have no control over the extent and continued use of data collected through Google’s use of DoubleClick. To the best of our knowledge, Google receives the information that you have accessed the relevant part of our website or have clicked on an ad from us. If you have a Google user account and are registered, Google may associate the visit with your user account. Even if you are not registered with Google or have not logged in, there is a chance that Google will learn and store your IP address.

You can prevent the installation of cookies by deleting existing cookies and deactivating the storage of cookies in the settings of your web browser. We point out that in this case you may not be able to use all functions of our website to the full extent. Preventing the storage of cookies is also possible by setting your web browser to block cookies from the domain “www.googleadservices.com” (https://www.google.com/settings/ads). We remind you that this setting will be deleted when you delete your cookies. You can also opt out of interest-based ads via the link http://www.aboutads.info/choices. Please be aware that this setting will also be deleted when you delete your cookies.

### Google AdSense

We use “Google AdSense”, an online advertising service of Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (hereinafter referred to as: “Google”) on our website. Among other things, Google AdSense uses cookies, small text files that are stored locally in the cache of your web browser on your device. Google uses a web beacon to set the cookie on your device. Your data will be transmitted to the USA and evaluated there. If you are logged in with your Google account, your data can be assigned directly to it. If you do not want to associate with your Google profile, you’ll need to log out. It is possible that these data may be shared with Google’s contractors to third parties and government agencies.

We use Google AdSense for marketing and optimization purposes, especially to show you relevant and interesting ads, improve campaign performance reports, or prevent you from seeing the same ads multiple times. This is also our legitimate interest in the processing of the above data, it is based on Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f) GDPR.

You can prevent the installation of cookies by deleting existing cookies and deactivating the storage of cookies in the settings of your web browser. We point out that in this case you may not be able to use all functions of our website to the full extent. Preventing the storage of cookies is also possible by disabling interest-based ads on Google through the link <https://www.google.com/ads/preferences>. We remind you that this setting will be deleted when you delete your cookies. You can also opt out of interest-based ads through the link <https://www.aboutads.info/choices>. Please be aware that this setting will also be deleted when you delete your cookies. If you use the Firefox, Internet Explorer or Google Chrome web browsers, you can permanently deactivate the setting of cookies at the following link: <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin>. We also point out that in this case you may not be able to use all functions of our website in full.

In addition, Google has submitted to the Privacy Shield Agreement between the European Union and the United States and certified. As a result, Google agrees to comply with the standards and regulations of European data protection law. Further information can be found in the following linked entry: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)

Further information on the use of data by Google, to hire and disagree as well as data protection can be found on the following websites of Google:

  * Privacy Policy: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy>
  * Advertising Privacy Policy: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads>

### Google AdWords

We use “Google Adwords,” a service of Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States (hereafter referred to as “Google”), on our website. Google Adwords enables us to use attractive advertising materials (so-called Google Adwords) on external websites to attract attention to our attractive offers. This allows us to determine how successful individual advertising measures are. These advertising materials are supplied by Google via so-called “ad servers”. We use so-called ad server cookies, which can be used to measure certain parameters for measuring success, such as the display of ads or clicks by the users. If you access our website via a Google ad, Google Adwords will save a cookie on your PC. These cookies usually lose their validity after 30 days. They are not meant to identify you personally. The following information is typically stored as analysis values ​​for this cookie: unique cookie ID, number of ad impressions per placement (frequency), last impression (relevant to post-view conversions), opt-out information (mark that the user does not want to be addressed anymore). These cookies allow Google to recognize your web browser. If a user visits certain pages of an Adwords customer’s website and the cookie stored on their computer has not expired, Google and the customer will be able to detect that the user clicked on the ad and was redirected to that page. Each Adwords customer is assigned a different cookie. Cookies cannot be tracked via the websites of Adwords customers. We ourselves do not collect and process any personal data in the aforementioned advertising measures. We receive only statistical evaluations provided by Google. On the basis of these evaluations, we can identify which of the advertising measures used are particularly effective. We do not receive any further data from the use of the advertising material, in particular we cannot identify the users on the basis of this information. Due to the marketing tools used, your browser automatically establishes a direct connection to the Google server. We have no control over the extent and continued use of data collected through the use of Google AdWords by Google. To the best of our knowledge, Google receives the information that you have accessed the relevant part of our website or have clicked on an ad from us. If you have a Google user account and are registered, Google may associate the visit with your user account. Even if you are not registered with Google or have not logged in, there is a chance that Google will learn and store your IP address.

We use Google AdWords for marketing and optimization purposes, especially to show you relevant and interesting ads, improve campaign performance reports, and achieve a fair calculation of advertising costs. This is also our legitimate interest in the processing of the above data, it is based on Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f) GDPR.

You can prevent the installation of cookies by deleting existing cookies and deactivating the storage of cookies in the settings of your web browser. We point out that in this case you may not be able to use all functions of our website to the full extent. Preventing the storage of cookies is also possible by setting your web browser to block cookies from the domain “www.googleadservices.com” (<https://www.google.com/settings/ads>). We remind you that this setting will be deleted when you delete your cookies. You can also opt out of interest-based ads through the link <https://www.aboutads.info/choices>. Please be aware that this setting will also be deleted when you delete your cookies.

In addition, Google has submitted to the Privacy Shield Agreement between the European Union and the United States and certified. As a result, Google agrees to comply with the standards and regulations of European data protection law. Further information can be found in the following linked entry: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)

Further information on the use of data by Google, to hire and disagree as well as data protection can be found on the following websites of Google:

  * Privacy Policy: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy
  * Google Website Stats: https: //services.google.com/sitestats/en.htm

### Facebook Pixel

We use “Facebook Pixel”, a service of Facebook Inc., 1601 S California Ave, Palo Alto, California 94304, USA (hereinafter referred to as: “Facebook”) on our website. Facebook Pixel allows Facebook to display our ads on Facebook, so-called “Facebook Ads” only to those Facebook users who have been visitors to our website, in particular those who have shown interest in our online offer or on certain topics or products. Facebook Pixels makes it possible to check whether a user has been redirected to our website after clicking on our Facebook Ads. Among other things, Facebook Pixel uses cookies, small text files that are stored locally in the cache of your web browser on your device. If you are logged in to Facebook with your user account, the visit to our online offer will be recorded in your user account. The data collected about you are anonymous to us, so do not give us any conclusions about the identity of the users. However, this data from Facebook can be linked to your local user account. We have no control over the extent and continued use of data collected through the use of Facebook Pixel by Facebook. To the best of our knowledge Facebook receives the information that you have accessed the relevant part of our website or have clicked on an advertisement from us. If you have a Facebook user account and are registered, Facebook can associate the visit with your user account. Even if you are not registered with Facebook or have not logged in, there is the possibility that Facebook will find out and save your IP address and any other identifying features.

We use Facebook Pixel for marketing and optimization purposes, especially to bring you relevant and interesting ads on Facebook, thus improving our offer, making it more interesting for you as a user and avoiding annoying ads. This is also our legitimate interest in the processing of the above data, this is based on Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f) GDPR.

You can object to the above-mentioned collection by Facebook Pixel as well as the use of your data to display Facebook Ads. To determine which types of ads you see on Facebook, please visit the following Facebook page: <https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads>.. We remind you that this setting will be deleted when you delete your cookies. In addition, you can deactivate cookies that serve the range measurement and advertising purposes via the following websites:

  * <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/>
  * <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>
  * <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices/>

Please be aware that this setting will also be deleted when you delete your cookies.

Facebook has subjected to the Privacy Shield Agreement concluded between the European Union and the United States and certified. As a result, Facebook commits to comply with the standards and regulations of European data protection law. For more information, please refer to the following linked entry: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active)

Further information from the third party on data protection can be found on the following Facebook page: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy>. Information about Facebook pixels can be found on the following Facebook page: <https://www.facebook.com/business/help/651294705016616>

## Affiliate Programs

We participate in serval Affiliate Program that give us the possibility to show specific advertisement to our customer in order to earn money through advertising reimbursement. Affiliate Programs require the uses of cookies to understand the origin of the orders.

The storage of “Affiliate cookies” is based on Art. 6 lit. f GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in this, since only through the cookies, the amount of its affiliate remuneration can be determined.

## Research

We may use the information you provide to invite you to participate in surveys and focus groups about our products, advertisers and services. Participation is always voluntary and the answers you provide are anonymous and aggregated to support our learnings and inform changes we can make to improve our products and services. Your data will not be added to any marketing lists unless you have consented to this and were informed at the point of capture and will only be shared with third parties where we have appointed them to manage research activity on our behalf.

## Links to third party websites

When you click on advertisements or links on any of our sites, you will leave that site and go to a third-party site, which is outside of our control. When we place an advertisement on one of our sites, it does not signify that we are endorsing that advertiser’s product or service. We do not accept responsibility for content, have no control over and our Privacy Policy does not apply to these companies, sites or content and if such third-party sites collect personal data, we cannot control how this data is processed, stored or used. We advise that you read their data collection statements, which accompany any registration and their Privacy Policies before you submit your personal information

## Legitimate Interest

We may process your personal data on the basis of a legitimate interest which may include promoting similar products or services via direct marketing activity, to manage suppression and unsubscribe requests received from you, to identify and prevent fraudulent behavior, maintaining the security of our system, data analytics, enhancing, modifying or improving our services, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of our campaigns.

Whenever we process data for these purposes we will ensure that we always keep your personal data rights in high regard and take account of these rights. Find out more about your rights and how to exercise them here.

We use servers located in the EEA to store data. When you submit your details and in whichever country you are situated you agree to the data being transferred to the EEA and processed under the terms of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (GDPR) including any implementing data protection legislation in Germany. If you are not in agreement please do not add your personal details on the website. We make no representation or warranty that the content and materials on the Website are appropriate or available for use in locations outside of Germany. Those who choose to access the Website or use the services from other locations do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent applicable.

Our security policies, rules and technical measures have been implemented to protect your personal information from unauthorized or improper use and from accidental loss.

All our employees and data processors that have access to, and are associated with, the processing of your personal information are legally obliged to respect the confidentiality of your data and are bound by contract to do so.

Note that some of our websites provide forums and commenting facilities where you can post information. When you do so, be aware that other visitors may collect any information you make public.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

We have formed partnerships with a variety of carefully selected companies that we share data with in order to carry out the activities described in the section How we Use your Data. Below is a non-exhaustive list of our key partners:

 **Fulfilment Partners:**

Pipedrive, Paypal,

 **Marketing Partners:**

Facebook, Twitter, Instagram

 **Advertising Technology Partners:**

Google, Facebook

 **Affiliate Partners:**

Amazon

We may also have to share your personal data with third parties whom we may choose to sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets. Alternatively, we may seek to acquire other businesses or merge with them. If a change happens to our business, then the new owners may use your personal data in the same way as set out in this Privacy Policy.

We will hold your personal information on our systems only for as long as required to provide you with the products and/or services you have requested.

Where you sign up to receive email marketing from us we will retain your e-mail address after you ‘opt-out’ of receiving emails in order to ensure that we continue to honor and respect that request. To unsubscribe from marketing emails at any time, please click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any marketing email and update your account preferences. You may also contact us to inform us if you do not wish to receive any marketing materials from us.

In some circumstances we may anonymize your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

You have the right to obtain information about the personal data stored by us at any time. You also have the right to transfer, rectify or delete, as well as to limit the processing of your data. Furthermore, you can object at any time to the processing of your data.

## Right to information

According to Art. 15 GDPR you have the right to ask us to confirm whether personal data concerning you are being processed. If so, you will continue to have a right to information about the personal data and information about the purpose of the processing, the category of personal data being processed, the recipients or categories of recipients to whom the personal data have been disclosed or disclosed the right of rectification or deletion of the data concerning you or the restriction of processing or right of objection to such processing, the existence of a right of appeal to a supervisory authority and, if personal Data was not collected from you, on all available information about the origin of the data.

## Right to rectification

According to Art. 16 GDPR you further have the right to demand without delay the correction or completion of incorrect personal data concerning you.

## Right to delete

Under the conditions specified in Art. 17 GDPR you have the right to demand the deletion of your personal data stored by us, except for the processing of the exercise of the right to freedom of expression and information, to fulfill a legal obligation, for reasons of public interest or to assert, exercise or defend legal claims.

## Right to restriction

Under the conditions of Art. 18 GDPR you have the right to demand the restriction of the processing of your data.

## Right to transmission

According to Art. 20 GDPR, you have the right to receive the personal data concerning you in a structured, common and machine-readable format, as well as the right, provided that the requirements of Art. 20 GDPR are met, to transfer them to another person in charge. In this context, you have the right to have the personal data relating to you transmitted directly to the other persons responsible.

## Right to objection

According to Art. 21 GDPR, provided that your personal data are based on legitimate interests in accordance with Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. f GDPR, the right to object to the processing of your personal data in accordance with Art. 21 GDPR, provided there are reasons for this arising from your particular situation.

Against the processing of your data for the purpose of the direct advertisement you have the right to contradict this processing at any time without indication of a special situation.

If you have an enquiry or concern about the contents of our Privacy Policy or our handling and use of your data, please email the Privacy Team on privacy@boxrox.com or send a letter to The Privacy Team, BOXROX, Alte Schönhauser Straße 38, 10119 Berlin, Germany. If you are not satisfied with our response to your enquiry or concern, you may wish to contact the Information Commissioner via their website

If we decide to change our Privacy Notice we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and in what circumstances we disclose it.

25th May 2018 – Policy Published
